[
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, why should you take notes during your research?",
    "answers": ["so you can organize your research"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Most research assignments tell you the exact topic you should write about.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement must have a topic and controlling idea.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? A thesis statement is optional in your research paper.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Creating an outline, either formal or informal, can help you organize your ideas so that you write a more logical research paper.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An outline must include Roman numerals and capital and lowercase letters to keep it organized.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? For academic research, you should write complete sentences when you take notes on an article.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or false? Most school library webpages have databases that anyone is free to use as long as they have an Internet connection.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the most academic kind of source?",
    "answers": ["library databases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of an annotated bibliography?",
    "answers": ["to help you summarize and evaluate your sources"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You must always use a formal outline to plan an effective research paper.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would be the most effective thesis statement for a research paper?",
    "answers": [
      "The U.S. government should require that all companies pay men and women the same amount of money for equal work."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? An annotated bibliography for a college class is always written in MLA format.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key to choosing good search terms?",
    "answers": ["think of several specific phrases to search"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: crime",
    "answers": ["auto-theft statistics in Chicago"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: national security",
    "answers": ["visa screening policies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for a more specific topic under the following general topic: urban development",
    "answers": ["smoking rules in public housing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the best search terms for the following topic: workplace ethics",
    "answers": ["paid paternity leave for new fathers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following internet sites would be acceptable to use when searching for sources for a research paper?",
    "answers": ["scholar.google.com"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a good search term for this topic: Topic: the economy",
    "answers": ["financial crisis of 2008"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lecture, where is the best place to look for sources for a research paper?",
    "answers": ["library databases"]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are questions to ask when determining reliability of a a source EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["How long is the source?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first thing to do after you receive a research paper assignment?",
    "answers": ["Think of a research question."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Most research papers share all of the following characteristics EXCEPT which one?",
    "answers": ["They are worth 150 pts."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Search engines like Google.com and Yahoo.com are the best places to do all your academic research.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a very good search term for this topic? Topic: Gun Laws",
    "answers": ["guns"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Every research assignment you will be assigned in college will have different requirements.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Every research paper must have at least one statistic to make the essay effective.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following groups of words is definitely not on the Academic Word List?",
    "answers": [
      "crash, cop, messy",
      "trashy, know-it-all, grouchy",
      "snooze, nerdy, lame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Statistics should not be used to start or end your body paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? It is ok to use contractions like \"can't\" and \"won't\" in your research paper so that you have more space on the pages to write about important ideas in your essay.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Statistics can be used to start body paragraphs.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phrase appropriate for an academic essay? in his article",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this expression appropriate for an academic essay? It's a piece of cake.",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? dummy",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? therefore",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? You should use as many academic words as possible in your research paper even if you don't know what all of them mean.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a reason to use a statistic in your research paper?",
    "answers": ["to make your paper longer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phrase appropriate for an academic essay? drunk as a skunk",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not an appropriate place to use a statistic in your research paper?",
    "answers": ["in the thesis statement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? y'all",
    "answers": ["No"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this word appropriate for an academic essay? increase",
    "answers": ["Yes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Purdue Owl?",
    "answers": [
      "It is a website with information to guide students in formatting their essays in MLA or APA format."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use this link to the Purdue Owl's MLA page to help you answer the following question. You will have to click on one of the tabs on the left menu of the webpage to find information about in-text citations. Purdue Owl MLA Which of the following does not use a correct MLA citation?",
    "answers": [
      "Romantic poetry is characterized by the \"spontaneous overflow of powerful feelings\" (Wordsworth, 1800, p. 263)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were using EasyBib to help you create a Works Cited entry for an electronic news source, and EasyBib gave you the results below, what additional information would you have to provide in order to create the citation?",
    "answers": ["article title, author, and publisher"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? EasyBib is free to use for formatting in MLA and APA.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is EasyBib?",
    "answers": [
      "It's a website that helps students format their Works Cited page or References list."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? If you paste a link to your online source in the EasyBib website, EasyBib will always supply all of the information you need to format your Works Cited entry.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the appropriate tab on the left to answer questions about creating a Works Cited page for book sources. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 9th ed., which of the following is not a correct Works Cited entry for a book?",
    "answers": ["Option:"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Works Cited Page: Other Common Sources tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 8th ed., which kind of source is this?",
    "answers": ["recorded television episode"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Abbreviations tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) According to MLA 9th ed. what is the correct way to write the month, January, in the publication date for a journal in a Works Cited page?",
    "answers": ["Jan."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click any tab you need to to answer the question below about this sample Works Cited page shown. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) In this Works Cited page using MLA 9th ed., which kinds of sources are A, B, and C? Choose the answer below that identifies all three sources correctly.",
    "answers": [
      "A. article with an author from an electronic source B. article with no author from an electronic source C. printed book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following link to the Purdue Owl website and click on the MLA Abbreviations tab on the left. Then scroll down to find the answer to the question below. Purdue Owl MLA (This will open in a new window.) True or False? According to MLA 9th ed., you should write the complete publisher's name for a book in your Works Cited page, but it's all right to omit words like \"Inc.\" or \"Corp.\"",
    "answers": ["True"]
  }
]
